question_data = [
    {
    "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
    "type": "boolean",
    "difficulty": "medium",
    "question": "DragonForce&#039;s &#039;Through the Fire and Flames&#039; is widely considered to be the hardest song in the Guitar Hero series.",
    "correct_answer": "True",
    "incorrect_answers": [
    "False"
    ]
    },
    {
    "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
    "type": "boolean",
    "difficulty": "medium",
    "question": "In the game &quot;Subnautica&quot;, a &quot;Cave Crawler&quot; will attack you.",
    "correct_answer": "True",
    "incorrect_answers": [
    "False"
    ]
    },
    {
    "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
    "type": "boolean",
    "difficulty": "medium",
    "question": "Mortal Kombat was almost based on Jean-Claude Van Damme movie.",
    "correct_answer": "True",
    "incorrect_answers": [
    "False"
    ]
    },
    {
    "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
    "type": "boolean",
    "difficulty": "medium",
    "question": "In Monster Hunter Generations, guild style is a type of hunting style.",
    "correct_answer": "True",
    "incorrect_answers": [
    "False"
    ]
    },
    {
    "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
    "type": "boolean",
    "difficulty": "medium",
    "question": "Resident Evil 4 was originally meant to be a Nintendo GameCube exclusive.",
    "correct_answer": "True",
    "incorrect_answers": [
    "False"
    ]
    },
    {
    "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
    "type": "boolean",
    "difficulty": "medium",
    "question": "In Portal, the Companion Cube&#039;s ARE sentient.",
    "correct_answer": "True",
    "incorrect_answers": [
    "False"
    ]
    },
    {
    "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
    "type": "boolean",
    "difficulty": "medium",
    "question": "In &quot;Starbound&quot;, the track played by the Decorated Music Box is named &quot;Atlas&quot;.",
    "correct_answer": "True",
    "incorrect_answers": [
    "False"
    ]
    },
    {
    "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
    "type": "boolean",
    "difficulty": "medium",
    "question": "In &quot;Call Of Duty: World At War&quot;, the first appearance of the &quot;PPSH-41&quot; in &quot;Zombies&quot; was in the map &quot;Der Riese&quot;.",
    "correct_answer": "False",
    "incorrect_answers": [
    "True"
    ]
    },
    {
    "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
    "type": "boolean",
    "difficulty": "medium",
    "question": "The Fiat Multipla is a drivable car in &quot;Forza Horizon 3&quot;.",
    "correct_answer": "False",
    "incorrect_answers": [
    "True"
    ]
    },
    {
    "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
    "type": "boolean",
    "difficulty": "medium",
    "question": "During pre-production of &quot;Super Mario Bros.&quot;, Mario originally was meant to shoot bullets.",
    "correct_answer": "True",
    "incorrect_answers": [
    "False"
    ]
    }
]